Southwest Folklore Center Cassette Recordings Collection, 1975-1995
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- The Cowboy Tour, The Cowboy Tour, 1983; Washington, DC., Produced by the National Council for the Traditional Arts, p1983; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph by Joe Wilson of the Cowboy Tour, taken at Judge Roy Bean's Jersey Lilly Saloon, Langtry, Texas, on cover...Performers include: Everett Brisendine; Duff Severe; Ken Trowbridge; Brownie Ford; Glenn Ohrlin; Junior Dougherty; Johnny Whenan; Karen Haleamau...A Part-time job -- The High-toned dance -- Old cowboys -- Streets of Laredo -- Bull Elk story -- The Cowboy's reincarnation -- Banks of the Ponchatrain -- A Second cold-nosed dog -- Boomer Johnson -- Bedridden in Arizona -- Jacinto Trevino -- Hanohano Olinda -- Away out there -- Sally Goodin -- Peñas clavadas -- Rodeo Romeo -- Kaula Ili -- Maiden's prayer --; SWF 83.25/C.1
- The Mormon Cowboy, Toelken, Barre, 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Tape contains a version of the Mormon Cowboy as performed by Barre Toelken...Tape is part of an open-ended collection of materials about the Mormon Cowboy available in acquisitions file, 83.26...; SWF 83.26/C.18
- Interview between James S. Griffith and Jim Officer, and Leonardo Yañez, "El Nano", Yañez, Leonardo, 1984; Douglas, AZ., Hotel Gadsten, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog, [vol.1]; NOTES: Interview conducted Jaunary 27, 1984... Acquisitions file contains Spanish transcription and English translations...Collector: James S. Griffith.; SWF 84.4/C.1
- Yañez interviews, Yañez, Leonardo, 1984; Douglas, AZ., Hotel Gadsten, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog, [vol.2]; NOTES: From acquisitions file: [James] Officer's back-up recording of interview with Leonardo Yañez, Douglas, Arizona, January, 27, 1984... File contains Spanish transcription and English translation... El moto de cumpas (performed by Los Doneños) -- Dos caballos Iamosos (performed by Gilberto Valenzuela, records the deaths of El Moro and Reámpago) --...Collector: James S. Griffith.; SWF 84.4/C.2
- Interview with Arnulfo D. Trejo and Marco Antonio Jerez, Trejo, Arnulfo D. and Marco Antonio Jerez, 1984; Tucson, AZ., University of Arizona Administration Building, March 6, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; From acquisitions file: "James Griffith and Celestino Fernandez (of the U. of A.'s sociology department)...interview...Marco Antonio Jerez and Arnulfo D. Trejo regarding their winning original entry, `El Corrido del Merino,' at the 1983 Tucson Meet Yourself corrido contest."...Collector: James S. Griffith and Celestino Fernandez.; SWF 84.7/C.1
- The Lore of the cowboy [in song and story], 1983; [Prescott, AZ.,] Sharlot Hall Museum, October 9, 1983; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquisition file: cassette tape of the "Lore of the cowboy" concert at Sharlot Hall Museum...Warren Miller interviews Everett Brisendine, Slim Kite, Bernetta Boot, and Gail Gardner...Songs and recitations include: Old cowboys never die (Everett Brisendine) -- Cowboy's dream (Slim Kite) -- When it's round-up time in Texas (Bernetta Boot) -- Cowboy's life (Gail Gardner) -- In memory of a pardner (Everett Brisendine) -- Sierry Petes (Gail Gardner) -- She'll be coming around the mountain (Everett Brisendine) -- Flop-eared mule (Slim Kite) -- Moonshine steer (Gail Gardner)...also includes a number of untitled stories...; SWF 84.8/C.1
- Tucson old time fiddle contest, Armory Park, February 26, 1984, 1984 February 26; Tucson, AZ., February 26, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquisitions file: Announcer, Loveless Gardner...Contestants include: Tony Cook; Dale Pauley; Jim Scodsdale; Darwin Long; Chuck Camp; Richard Spenser...Transcript is available in acquisitions file 84.10/C.1...Collector: James S. Griffith.; SWF 84.10/C.1
- Cliff Edwards Interview and songs, Edwards, Cliff, 1984 May 10; Coolidge, AZ., May 10, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquisitions file: Recorded at the home of Mrs. Bessie Henley, Coolidge, Arizona...Interview with and songs by Cliff Edwards, retired "cowboy and barnstormer"...More information regarding Mr. Edwards and a transcript of the interview available in 84.13/C.1.T...City boy's life in a country town -- The Cowboy's prayer -- The Strawberry roan -- The Zebra dun --Collector: James S. Griffith.; SWF 84.13/C.1
- Bring back the cowboys, Biddy, Dr. John D.C., 1983; 1983; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Transcription located in acquisitions file... Bring back the cowboys --; SWF 84.14/C.1
- Interview with Harold Morgan, Morgan, Harold, 1984 August 18; Cornville, AZ., August 18, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Interview by Warren Miller... Acquistion file includes transcription of interview and song lyrics... Hobo Jack's last ride -- untitled -- untitled -- The Yellow Rose of Texas -- Wreck of the Royal Palm -- untitled -- Little Joe -- Untitled -- Why do you bob your hair, girls? -- Save my mother's picture from the sale -- T for Texas, T for Tennessee -- The Banks of the Old Oak Creek --Collector: Warren Miller.; SWF 84.14/C.2
- Interview with Harold Miller, Miller, Harold, 1984 August 17; Cornville, AZ., August 17, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Interview with Harold Morgan by Warren Miller... Transcript located in acquisitions file... Poems and songs include: untitled (poem) -- Come sit by my side little darling (song) -- I'll fly away (song) -- untitled (song) -- When the work's done this fall (song) -- untitled (song) -- untitled (song) -- The Hobo and the Angelus (poem) -- If you'll let me be your little sweetheart (song) -- untitled (song) -- Tobacco song (song) ---Collector: Warren Miller.; SWF 84.14/C.3
- Interview with Ross Knox, Knox, Ross, 1984 August 21; Grand Canyon Caverns, AZ., August 21, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Interview with Ross Knox by Warren Miller... Acquisition file includes transcript... Poems include: Hollywood bound -- Yavapia Pete -- untitled -- The Cowboy's prayer -- Easy chairs and saddle sores -- Git put in a double harness -- So long -- Cold and lonely -- untitled -- The Dying times --Collector: Warren Miller.; SWF 84.14/C.4
- Interview with Harold Morgan, Morgan, Harold, 1984 August 31; Cornville, AZ., August 31, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Interview with Harold Morgan by Warren Miller... Acquisition file includes transcripts... Songs include: The Unclouded day -- untitled -- untitled -- untitled -- Put my little shoes away -- untitled -- untitled -- Silver-haired Daddy of mine -- Mother was a lady (or, If Jack were only here) -- Little boy of mine -- No one will ever know -- Too late -- Muleskinner blues -- My curly-headed baby -- untitled -- untitled -- Silver threads among the gold -- Instrumental untitled --Collector: Warren Miller.; SWF 84.14/C.5
- Interview with Clyde Wamsley, Wamsley, Clyde, 1984 September 28; Taylor, AZ., September 28, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Interview with Clyde Wamsley by Warren Miller... Transcript located in acquisition file...Songs include: Sierra Pete -- untitled -- Strawberry roan -- untitled --; SWF 84.14/C.6
- Interview with Earl Rogers, Rogers, Earl, 1984 October 3; Tonto Flat, AZ., October 3, 1984 and October 26, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Interview by Warren Miller...Collector: Warren Miller; SWF 84.14/C.7
- Interview with Harold Morgan, Morgan, Harold, 1984 November 9; Cornville, AZ., November 9, 1984, 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Interview with Harold Morgan by Warren Miller... transcript located in acquisition file... Songs and poems include: Nobody's darling but mine (song) -- Too late (song) -- Train whistle blues (song) -- Waiting for a train (song) -- Way out there (poem) -- Tumblin weeds (song) -- Fraulein (song) -- untitled (song) -- We sat beneath the maple on the hill (song) -- I'm so lonesome I could cry (song) --Collector: Warren Miller; SWF 84.14/C.8
- Interview with Ross Knox, Knox, Ross, 1984 November 23; Seligman, AZ., November 23, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog, tape 2; NOTES: Interview with Ross Knox by Warren Miller... transcript located in acquisition file... Poems include: The Old nighthawk -- The Experiment -- Windy Bill -- Women drivers -- The Long-eared bull -- Little blue roan -- Brewery Gulch Gazette -- Bear ropin' buckaroo -- The Ridge running roan -- The Hell-bound train -- Cowboy's prayer -- The Cowboy's dream --Collector: Warren Miller; SWF 84.14/C.9
- Interview with Ross Knox, Knox, Ross, 1984 November 23; Seligman, AZ., November 23, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog, tape 2; NOTES: Interview with Ross Knox by Warren Miller... transcript located in acquisition file... Poems include: Git put in a double harness -- Hollywood bound -- Easy chairs and saddle sores -- Cold and lonely -- The Dying times -- So long -- Going home -- untitled --Collector: Warren Miller; SWF 84.14/C.10
- Interview with Harry Taylor, Taylor, Harry, 1984 December 3; Scottsdale, AZ., December 3, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Interview with Harry Taylor by Warren Miller... transcript located in acquisition file... Poems include: Murph and McClop -- untitled -- The U-P train -- Zebra dun -- Tying knots in the devil's tail -- Windy Bill --Collector: Warren Miller; SWF 84.14/C.11
- Interview sith Dave Ericcson and Duane Reese, Ericcson, Dave and Duane Reese, 1984 December 7; Alamo, AZ., December 7, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Interview with Dave Ericcson and Duane Reese by Warren Miller... transcript located in acquisition file... Poems include: Silver bells and golden spurs -- The Little blue roan -- An Experiment -- The Long-eared bull -- No imposter -- The Cowboy's dream -- Collector: Warren Miller; SWF 84.14/C.12
- Interview with Ross Knox, Knox, Ross, 1985 February 1; Elko, NV; February 1, 1985; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Interview with Ross Knox by James S. Griffith at the Cowboy Poetry Gathering... transcript located in acquisition file... Poems include: The Old nighthawk -- An Experiment -- Women drivers -- D-2 Horse wrangler -- Prairie Gulch Gazette or Star -- Little blue roan -- Collector: James S. Griffith; SWF 84.14/C.13
- Arizona cowboy poets, Miller, Warren, Duane Reece, Everett Brisendine, and Ross Knox, 1985 February 2; Elko, NV; February 1, 1985; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Recorded on February 2, 1985 in Elko, Nevada at the Cowboy Poetry Gathering...The Arizona presentation performers include: Warren Miller; Duane Reece; Everett Bridendine; Ross Knox...Cowboy sign (Duane Reece) -- Untitled (Everett Brisendine) -- Untitled (Ross Knox) -- The Old nighthook (Ross Knox) -- No imposter (Duane Reece) -- To a wonderful lady (Everett Brisendine) -- Git put in a double harness (Ross Knox) -- Hollywood bound (Ross Knox) --Collector: James S. Griffith; SWF 84.14/C.14
- Interview with Melvin Whipple about the Arizona Strip, Whipple, Melvin, 1985 February 2; Elko, NV; February 1, 1985; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: James S. Griffith interviews Melvin Whipple of Hereford, Texas on February 2, 1985 at the Cowboy Poetry Gathering in Elko, Nevada...Acquisitions file includes transcription of conversation and recitations...Majority of interview comprises reminiscences of ranching in the Arizona Strip from the 1930's to 1950's...Poetry includes: Bad night on the Seals Ranch -- Washes in the night --Collector: James S. Griffith; SWF 84.14/C.15
- Favorite cowboy recitations: Cowboy poets and their poems, Cowboy Poetry Gathering, Salt Lake City, UT., Utah Folklife Center; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: First Annual Cowboy Poetry Gathering in Elko, Nevada...The Cowboy's prayer (Owen Johnson) -- Strawberry roan (Ray Lashley) -- Zebra dun (Larry Schutte) -- Shag Brauntay (Bud Bartram) -- Home sweet home (Sam Scheyler) -- Murph and McClop (Harry Taylor) -- The Courtship of young Waddie (Randy Stowell) -- The Flying outlaw (Waddie Mitchell) -- Old times (Ken Trowbridge) -- Cowboy's dream or Frost on the cowboy's harp (Dave Ericsson) -- The Bronco twister's prayer (Yula S. Hunting) -- Sellin' Prewitt's cow (Baxter Black) -- The Rodeo trail (Buck Crofts) -- The Kid solos (Bob Schilds) -- Cows and logs (Harold Otto) -- Early morning roundup (Harold Otto) -- The old cowman (Dick Gibford) -- So long (Ross Knox) -- Open range (Melvin Whipple) -- The Lowly brawl (Vern Mortensen) -- Then and now (Jack Walther) -- Cowboys of yesteryear (Cecil Moore) -- How many cows (Nyle Henderson) -- No imposters (Duane Reece) -- Reincarnation (Wallace McRae) --Collector: Warren Miller; SWF 84.14/C.16
- Interview with Earnest L. Johnson, Johnson, Earnest L., 1984 July 27; Salt Lake City, UT., Utah Folklife Center; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Interview with Earnest L. Johnson by Warren Miller in Mesa, Arizona, July 27, 1984...Acquisition file includes transcript of interview...Poems: Ready to work -- Untitled --Collector: Warren Miller; SWF 84.14/C.17
- Interview with Huland Rogers, Rogers, Huland, 1984 August 4; Salt Lake City, UT., Utah Folklife Center; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Interview with Huland Rogers by Warren Miller on August 4, 1984...Acquisition file includes transcript of interview...Songs: Riding down the canyon -- Back in the saddle again -- Untitled -- I got spurs that jingle -- Untitled -- Roundup time in Texas --Collector: Warren Miller; SWF 84.14/C.18
- Interview with Harold Adams, Adams, Harold, 1984 July 26; Cottonwood, AZ., July 26, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Interview with Harold Adams by Warren Miller in Cottonwood, Arizona on July 26, 1984...Acquisition file includes transcript of interview...Songs: Pride of the prairie, Mary -- Little old rag doll -- Roll on little doggie -- I just come back to say goodbye -- Collector: Warren Miller; SWF 84.14/C.19
- Old songs and poetry, Edwards, Cliff, 1984 August 14; Coolidge, AZ., August 14, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquisitions file: Recording was sent from Cliff Edwards containing songs and recitations written for the University of Arizona...Quality of tape is poor...More information regarding the contents and transcriptions available in acquisitions file, 84.19/C.1.T...Mormon cowboy -- Drunk cowboy, crossing the Isles of Peru -- Poem about Hell in Arizona -- The Flying U Bull -- The Cabalerio -- The Cowboy's prayer -- A City boy's life in a country town -- Strawberry roan -- Zebra dun -- Hobo Bill's last ride -- All aroud [sic] the water tank -- Frankie and Johnnie --Collector: James S. Griffith; SWF 84.19/C.1
- Interview with Bill Thompson, Thompson, Bill, 1984 [?]; Morenci, AZ., [1984?]; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Acquisition file includes transcription of songs...From Acquisition Inventory, "songs concern Clifton-Morenci area miners' strike and flood"...Good old Morenci -- Clifton will rise again --; SWF 84.20/C.1
- Interview with and recitals by Bill Moore, Moore, Bill, 1984 September 12; Cortaro, AZ., September 12, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Interview by James S. Griffith with Bill Moore on September 12, 1984, at the Lazy K Bar Guest Ranch...Acquisition file includes transcript of interview...Recitations: Moccasin Mick -- Old Glory Trail -- The Cowboy and the shephard -- Face on the barroom floor -- untitled --Collector: James S. Griffith.; SWF 84.21/C.1
- Lalo Guerrero with the Mariachi Colonial, Guerrero, Lalo, 1984; p1984; Lalo Guerrero, 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Written and recorded by Guerrero in an election-year effort to get Mexicans, Mexican Americans, and Chicanos to register to vote...Acquisition file contains English transcription of songs...Battle cry of the Chicano -- Himno Chicano...In English and Spanish...; SWF 84.22/C.1
- Interview with Buster Bailey, Bailey, Buster, 1984 October 5; Tucson, AZ., October 5, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: One cassette tape of songs, recitations, harmonica solos, and interview with Buster Bailey...Songs in old cowboy style...Interview takes place behind Allen's Auto Parts, Tucson, AZ...Acquisition file includes typed transcript of interview interspersed with songs...Zebra Dun -- Wreck of the old '97 (harmonica solo) -- Little Joe, the wrangler (harmonica solo) -- Sierra peaks (Tying the knot in the devil's tail) -- Back to the dogs and horses (recitation) -- Whiskey toast (recitation) -- Poem justifying drinking (recitation) -- Billy Venero (fragment) -- Rye whiskey -- Frozen logger -- Old Smokey -- Little Mohea -- Days of '49 --Collector: James S. Griffith.; SWF 84.25/C.1
- Pachuco [language], Barker, George C., Tucson, AZ., October 5, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquisitions file: This tape recording has been dubbed from orignal recordings made on paper tape that are located in the George C. Barker Collection...Recording contains examples of..."Pachuco: An American-Spanish argot"...Pachuco is a language used by Tucson-area gangs in the 1940's...More information is available in the George C. Barker manuscript collection...; SWF 85.2/C.1
- Interview with Lalo Guerrero, Guerrero, Lalo, 1985 April 23; April 23, 1985; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From Acquisitions Inventory: Recording contains interview with Lalo Guerrero..."concerning his early Tucson career [and] perceptions of his compositions"...Collector: James S. Griffith.; SWF 85.10/C.1
- Lalo Guerrero, songs, Guerrero, Lalo, 1985 April; April, 1985; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Tape contains dubbed songs from original 45 rpm discs...Complete list of recordings is available in Acquisitions Inventory, including record master number and publishing company...In Spanish...Llego muy crudo el Grenudo -- Busco una novia -- El Gordobes -- En la cantina -- La Flaca -- Malas jugadas -- La Mini flada de Reyalda -- Lagrimas de Borracha -- Ya supe Lupe -- Punalada trapira -- La Pollera rota -- El Camino de amor -- Lamento de soltero -- Ya supe Lupe -- Ven, corazon -- Rock'n roll de nino -- El Caballo blanco -- El Bikini de Tia Trini -- Un Marciano en la tierra -- Una Penalada -- Ole -- Seis canciones -- El Pajaro Cu-Cu -- No la dejo de querer -- No naci pa'soldado -- Soldado raso -- Palomita morenita -- El Brujo -- Virgen morena -- El Feo --; SWF 85.12/C.1
- Lalo Guerrero, songs, Guerrero, Lalo, 1985 April; April, 1985; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Tape contains dubbed songs from original 45 rpm discs...Complete list of recordings is available in Acquisitions Inventory, including record master number and publishing company...In Spanish...Llego muy crudo el Grenudo -- Busco una novia -- El Gordobes -- En la cantina -- La Flaca -- Malas jugadas -- La Mini flada de Reyalda -- Lagrimas de Borracha -- Ya supe Lupe -- Punalada trapira -- La Pollera rota -- El Camino de amor -- Lamento de soltero -- Ya supe Lupe -- Ven, corazon -- Rock'n roll de nino -- El Caballo blanco -- El Bikini de Tia Trini -- Un Marciano en la tierra -- Una Penalada -- Ole -- Seis canciones -- El Pajaro Cu-Cu -- No la dejo de querer -- No naci pa'soldado -- Soldado raso -- Palomita morenita -- El Brujo -- Virgen morena -- El Feo --; SWF 85.12/C.2
- Pachuco corridos of Lalo Guerrero, Guerrero, Lalo, 1985; 1985; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquisitions file: El pachuco -- Nuestro idioma -- El pachuco y el Tarzan -- El pachuco, el Tarzan, y el Charrasqueado --La Boda de los pachucos -- Los Chucos suaves -- Chicas patas boogie -- Marijuana boogie --; SWF 85.13/C.1
- Pachuco and related material, tape 1, Guerrero, Lalo, 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquisitions file: Los dos carnales -- El Mojado -- El Piscador -- Ya me voy para Korea -- El Soldado -- El Hombre gordo -- Yo soy el bato -- Mi guerita -- Chicas patas boogie -- [title unknown] -- Las Mujeres -- Chicana -- El Hijo de Juan Charrasqueado -- [title unknown] -- [title unknown] -- Nuestra idioma -- Los Dos carnales -- El Pachuco -- El Pachuco y el Tarzan -- El Pachuco, el Tarzan, y el Charrasqueado -- El Tirilongo -- Maldita suerte del pachuco -- Las Comadres pachucas -- [title unknown] -- La Boda de los pachucos -- Marijuana boogie -- Los Chucos suaves -- [title unknown] -- [title unknown] --; SWF 85.13/C.2
- Pachuco and related material, tape 2, Guerrero, Lalo, 1985; 1985; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquisitions file: Me fui pa Califa -- [title unknown] -- [title unknown] -- [title unknown] -- [title unknown] -- Mi guirita -- Chicas patas boogie -- [title unknown] -- Las Mujeres -- La Chicana -- El Hijo de Juan Charrasqueado -- [title unknown] -- Me fue pa Califa -- [title unknown] --; SWF 85.13/C.3
- Pachuco corridos of Lalo Guerrero, Guerrero, Lalo, 1985; 1985; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquisitions file: Las Comadres pachucas -- [title unknown] -- La Boda de los pachucos -- Marijuana boogie -- Los Chucos suaves -- Chicas patas boogie -- [title unknown] --; SWF 85.13/C.4
- Lalo Guerrero Trio and Zoot Suit, Lalo Guerrero Trio, 1985; 1985; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquisitions file: La Boda de los pachucos -- Marijuana boogie -- Los Chucos suaves -- [title unknown] -- [title unknown] -- [title unknown] -- El Piscador -- Ya me voy para Korea -- El Soldado -- El Hombre gordo -- Yo soy el vato -- [title unknown] -- [title unknown] -- [title unknown] -- Nuestro idioma -- [title unknown] -- El Pachuco y el Tarzan -- El pachuco, el Tarzan y el Charrasqueado -- El Tirilongo -- [title unknown] -- Maldita suerte del pachuco -- Las Comadres pachucas -- [title unknown] --; SWF 85.13/C.5
- Lalo Guerrero: Disney sessions, Guerrero, Lalo, 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Acquisitions file inludes transcriptions of the songs Pancho rock -- Rosita -- Mickey Mouse mambo -- Tacos for two -- Message from Garcia -- I would rather cha-cha -- I adore you -- 16 pounds -- Reincarnation -- Down in México City -- Bullfight -- Poor people of Juarez -- Pancho Lopez -- Hey Mabel -- Rock and roll Rita --; SWF 85.13/C.6
- Lalo Guerrero: Bits and pieces, Guerrero, Lalo, 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Acquisition file includes written introduction by Charlie Blenman and transcripts of the songs...El Sonorense -- La Burrita -- El Sonorense -- La Burrita -- [title unknown] -- Feliz Año Nuevo -- Asi como el sol -- El Bolerito --; SWF 85.13/C.7.T
- The 1935 Grand Canyon Cowboy Band, The Grand Canyon Cowboy Band, 1985; Prescott, AZ., Produced by Warren Miller, Sharlot Hall Museum, 1985; 1 sound cassette (45 min.), analog; NOTES: Cover includes biographical information about the Grand Canyon Cowboy Band... Performers include: Marvin Bennet; John Bradley; Sam Fenner; Slim Kite... Howdy -- Hell among the Yearlings -- Ridin' down the canyon -- Cowboy's dream -- Kelly waltz -- All aboard for that Bright Angel Trail -- Goin' up Cripple Creek -- Preacher story -- Burglar boy -- Tumblin' tumbleweeds -- Bad brahma bull -- Carry me back to mammmy -- Slim's first guide trip -- Sierry Petes, Cajun bird dog story -- Kiss me again waltz -- Phantom Ranch dream -- Mustang with wings -- Texas wagoner -- Marvin's pup dog -- Flop-eared mule -- Don't sell that cow -- The Moonshine steer -- Soldier's joy -- Vera, the queen of the canyon -- Platonia, pride of the plains -- Roll on --; SWF 85.17/C.1
- Centennial Pageant, 1885.1985, Colonia Juarez Stake Centennial Pageant, 1885.1985, Produced by the Centennial Committee [1985?]; 1 sound cassette, analog; Juarez Stake centennial hymn -- Pioneer medley -- Albert's decision -- La Paloma -- Way down in Mexico -- Oh say what is truth -- Dark and drear the skies appear -- Old maid's song -- After the ball -- God moves in a mysterious way -- Adelita -- God be with you -- Southern dreams -- Our heritage --; SWF 85.19/C.1
- Yaqui Pahkola and Deer music, 1985 April; Patam, Mexico, April, 1985; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Recording contains Yaqui Pahkola and Deer music from Potam, Mexico...; SWF 85.20/C.1